here's what I want you guys to do I want
you to stand up and I want you to help
me welcome to the stage by far one of
the best people when it comes to sales
psychology webinars and selling as he
says one to many ladies and gentlemen
Jason
[Applause]
flatl oh come on you guys are too kind
wo one to many I think somebody just did
a launch like one to many challenge you
guys see that good you didn't see that
right cuz that's my
[__] offers and objections these are two
things that matter more than anything
else in your webinars uh at me at
Instagram I just started doing this
stuff I made millions of dollars I got
thousands of followers that's [__] up
we got to fix that okay I got 60 Minutes
to spit as much game to you as I
possibly can today it says 50 on the on
the on the confidence monitor can we get
that 60 would that be I I can't do this
for 50 I got I got a I might be selling
something today so I need those 10
minutes to close the smartest people in
the room it's about 40 of you the rest
of you aren't smart enough to buy but
maybe the 40 of you in the room are
smart enough to buy so I got to do that
too so we'll see if I can do it or not
I'm going to teach you fill in the blank
formulas I'm going to show you bonus
hacks I'm going to give you copy in case
closes I'm going to turn objections into
Alchemy and give you the greatest cell
sequence ever ever and don't try to take
pictures of these slides you won't be
able to I have over 200 slides here
today to go through okay you want the
slides come up to me I'm a nice guy I'm
handsome I'm charismatic I'm witty and
I'll give them to you all
right now where these secrets come from
in brief I went through 32 different
seven figure webinars I've wrote in the
last 16 years if you know somebody who's
wrote more than 32 s figure webinars let
me know I will pay them whatever money I
have to to learn from them but I don't
think anybody else has now uh Joe McCall
is he here are you here two years ago I
forgot about this in a drunken stup he
says hey Jason if you put together your
best webinar slide decks I would pay you
a gigantic pile of money for that right
he's like ah I totally forgot about that
because then I did it and I didn't
follow up and sell you sorry I will fix
that here today
okay uh I ran and pretty much
masterminded and ran point on the
biggest launch in internet marketing
history $57 million from scratch in 226
days Daniel Hall Ashley Armstrong they
were part of the team that made that
happen we all kick some ass together
yeah yeah yeah yeah we did that and then
we did that with $400 in
advertising yeah stupid actually like if
we would have spent money I think we
could have made more but uh I'm a [__]
up in more ways than I'm brilliant I'm
brilliant at a few things and I'm
autistic at the the rest of my life okay
so I do what I can with what I can right
so onik was telling about ASM this was
the biggest promotion asm5 we did 9.8
million in eight days or as I prefer to
say we did $7 million more than second
place that makes me feel a little bit
better about that that's why they kicked
us off the leaderboard they said here's
the first prize you get it now bow out
of the
competition now I remember I was really
pissed about the kosaki deal because
they're like kosaki is going to do
bigger numbers than you because he has 4
Mill ion followers we had 40,000
followers right um when we did the plan
we had 200,000 followers so we're
putting up numbers without Tony Robin
Style 2 million people opting into a
launch I know how to get a lot out of a
little and I remember being so pissed
off about what they said about kosaki
that I'm like I'm going to help onic
beat him just to prove it wrong I'm
Petty like that just like anik is petty
like that right one of the things I told
anik it's a stupid idea but it works so
well as I said if one webinar is good
just do two
webinars to the same audience so sell
them this way if they don't buy then
sell them that way I don't know just
seems to make a lot of sense to me but
nobody was doing that back then we were
doing three webinars cart open cart
closed and somewhere in the middle and
this kind of helps so I'm going to give
you some secrets from that you might
know this guy's name is Alex Heros he
pays me for Consulting to help him with
his offers and with his webinars and so
these secrets have been battle tested in
varieties in different situations Zoom
themselves have brought me in to help
them and they're billion dooll companies
so I think I kind of maybe can do a
little bit of cool stuff here today you
know what I want though what do I
want you guys say sales right I want
money more important than the money I
want the
result I want you to say a year from now
two years from now six months from now
60 seconds from now I learned this thing
from Jason I applied it it made me a big
amount of money and then tell me about
it is that fair okay I've had people
literally make over $100 million with my
stuff and not tell me about
it I it makes me sad CU I'm like am I
really that good I don't think I'm that
good I need your testimonials so that
way I can continue to have this big ass
ego that I have all right because I'm
kind of a big deal all
right my focus today offers and
objections these are the two things that
matter the most when it comes to
webinars the rest is just details this
is the two things that matter the most
now why do I say these two things matter
the most here's the quick story of why
this guy on the right his name is Dylan
Frost he runs a program called the
wholesale formula I write and deliver
the webinar for it I'm the spokesman
it's a great business model I do it two
times a year I deliver the webinar I
make a gigantic pile of money millions
of dollars he makes millions of dollars
we're both very happy Dylan says to me
if I get this guy to promote you will
you do a new webinar training program
this guy being Jeff Walker one of the
finest human beings to exist in this
business product launch formula Creator
and and I said yeah I'll do it because
I'm eight years overdue because the last
webinar program I ever bought or created
before that was genius webinars was is
really good but it's eight years old I
could fill six more books up in the time
that I learned from 2017 when I created
this product so I said okay let's do it
Jeff agrees Jeff promotes and I said if
I'm going to do it this time I'm going
to go back through every single webinar
I've ever written in my life find every
technique and every strategy that I can
and put it in this training program so I
did what's called A Hard Target search
you ever seen the movie The Fugitive he
goes we're going to look at every
Penthouse every ous every Warehouse
every dogghouse until we find the
greatest webinar Alchemy that's ever
existed that's what I did it was
miserable I hated life for 50 hours but
when I was done oh my God I got some
game I got some knowledge and what I
discovered was two things became more
clear to me than ever before some of
these things I did unconscious
they became conscious my best webinars
were the ones where I crushed the
objections and I crushed the offers I
became convinced as I was looking at
some of these webinars because some of
these webinars that put up millions of
dollars I was looking at them like these
[__] suck I'm like they're not very
good I'm like I I didn't know how to
speak at a fifth grade level I was
speaking like a college professor and I
was making all these weird intellectual
and obtuse arguments and I'm like this
is stupid but then as long as they got
to the offer it didn't really really
matter what I said before then they're
like this offer is so good I'll buy
despite not because of you and I'm like
oh it's just it's the objection stupid
right it's it's the economy stupid
that's why presidents get elected this
is how products get bought offers and
objections I've coached more people on
webinars at a higher level than anyone
on the planet and I realize this no one
does what I do with objections I will
prove that to you for example 17
objections in the introduction most you
don't even address 17 objections in the
entirety of your webinar I'm just
getting started right I intentionally
create objections in the content you
know what's the best objections to close
the ones that you set up in
advance so you ever heard seven plus or
minus two so psychologist says you can
hold seven bits of information in your
mind at once plus or minus two the
smarter ones can hold nine the Dumber
ones can hold five right okay how many
fingers am I holding up if you f okay
good good what about now nine some
people will still say five like okay we
know who's who so if I can give you the
five to nine objections to hold in your
mind I can control the objections you
have in your mind and if I have the best
answers to those objections and you
can't object to other things I win so
this is the kind of stuff that we do
Transition I actually create objections
before I go into the sale okay what's
the natural state of being when somebody
hears an offer like emotionally
physically how do most people feel when
they hear an
offer they're resistant towards it yeah
so I just create the resistance for them
and then I crush the resistance so I
don't try to fight the resistance that's
what rookies do I agitate the resistance
I take the natural state they're going
to be in anyway and I amplify it and
then boom I close close off of that
we'll talk about that right and then
when we close this is the offer what to
speak of how we deal with objections in
the offer which is what our focus is
going to be on for the next 20ish so
minutes so this is the bestselling book
of all time on offers by Alex Hermos
sold over a million copies and it's an
interesting book because before he wrote
this book he sent me this text message
one day and it goes like this he says
Jason Alex Heros here you may not
remember me this is how long this goes
back but you changed my life says you
came up to us and you said when it's
easy is when you go hard so if you ever
heard him referen that in his social
media that's what happened I said when
it's the easiest you can ever make money
is when you should work the hardest most
of you got it twisted you work hard when
it's hard and then when it gets easy you
take a break but that's where all the
momentum is but then he goes on and says
something else that I find fascinating
he says I just stumbled upon your
webinar course this was genius webinars
not goat webinars and he says it's the
single best course on offer Creation in
Persuasion and I've milked that
testimonial ever
since cuz if this if the bestselling
author author on planet
Earth if he says I have the best thing
for it kind of a kind of a good point
that he's making there right and I think
I've done better since then but you know
that was old news that was 2018 the
world goes on but he said offer creation
he pulled what I taught about offers
which was one section of webinars
generalized it to all of marketing and
sold a million books
insane and he learned it from me so
would you like me to teach you a better
version than what I taught
Alex yeah and then when one of you son
of a [__] write another book that
sells a million copies just [__]
dedicate it to me
okay I mean Alex quoted me in this more
than anybody else which is nice every
time he sells 10 books I sell one book
so I can't complain but hopefully you
can outsell Alex with this offer has
five parts at the end of the day the
core of the price the bonuses the risk
and the scarcity this is where gets
exciting because we break it down to its
first principles its simplest elements
when you make the core part of your
offer in your webinar here's what your
audience should think whoa this will
best help me do what you just showed me
on the webinar so this is the extension
of the content the core should be
extension of the content you spent 45
minutes teaching them something that got
them excited and then the core offer is
this is how you best utilize and use
what I just taught you and that's what
the core does and then when you reveal
the price if you do it correctly the the
person says wow what a great deal not oh
my God that's a lot of money they say
what a great deal and then you drop the
bonuses and then they say oh my God now
I must buy I was thinking about buying
before but now I must buy and then you
show the risk and they say whoa it's
actually more expensive not to
buy big secret for you there I make more
sales when people run out of excuses to
not buy then have reasons to buy they
say [__] I can't I can't do it it's
going to cost me more than not to buy
and then they buy and then the scarcity
says I must buy
now so they go I should buy I will buy I
must buy and I must buy now and that's
how I think about it whenever I create
an offer for myself or for my clients
you'll take in pictures put that [__]
away you're going to miss out on the
game this is 2D this is 3D I want you to
be immersive because I want
your money or result uh both okay we'll
call it both right now if you put it on
a timeline timeline looks like this core
price bonuses risk was scarcity
sprinkled throughout like judiciously
like a nice fine salt okay core 3 to
five minutes price 3 to five minutes
bonus 10 to 15 minutes risk 15 minutes
to four
hours I don't know how bad some of
youall want to make money right after we
did the plan did the $7 million launch I
get on with Evan Pagan he's got this
group of people Ballers all of them he
says Jason get on tell tell them what
you did for the launch that was so
successful I said let me tell you what I
did for the launch right and then I
explained to them how the average
webinar was 4 to 6 hours long because
the majority of it was dealing with
objections and I'm thinking the audience
is going to be like thank you Jason for
sharing this audience was like oh that
sounds like a lot of work I'm like [__]
out of here with this right of course
it's a lot of work everything's a lot of
work there's just high paid work and low
paid work but it's all work and then I
thought about it again I said you know
what good when you quit is when I take
your
customers so please keep thinking that
because I'll please keep doing what I'm
doing when anik and I are on a webinar
battling out closes and my my business
partner will says it's not fair it's not
fair a customer can't stand one good
closer you put two closers against their
biggest excuse and it goes away just
like magic but this is typically the
sequence of how we do things you want to
break it down
okay all right yes yes please okay this
is some science for you most people
don't get this they don't realize this I
put the price up front of my offers I
don't put it at the end if you're
putting your price at the end change
that [__] I promise you you will make
more money I promise you you will make
more money if you read it later in a
book that Russell Brunson wrote remember
it came from me first okay but it will
make you more
money I'm going to give you one frame I
have multiple frame if you have one tool
in the toolkit it only works for one
job I would rather have multiple tools
in the toolkit because then I could
handle multiple jobs so this is just one
frame that I could teach you very
quickly when introducing the core offer
story assumption overview breakdown
access even though this I think is
incredibly simple I think it will be
profound for some of you then we can
build up on it maybe later story goes
like this you were where they are so you
once were them so they can see the
journey at the beginning of the offer
and then the assumption is they will do
what you did to get to where you are
what do they need to do as part of that
to get to where you are they need
to invest right didn't you invest to get
where you were at okay show me one
person who didn't buy a course to help
them get to where they are right now in
this room did anybody in this room get
success without first buying something
no all of you had to buy something in
order to transform sometimes you forget
it and then you can't close on it
because you don't think about it but I
say what made the difference was when I
made my first big investment to work
with the right Menor who gave me no
other option but to succeed and I want
to extend that beautiful gift to you as
well this is how you close I said what
is the beautiful gift that I'm extending
to them what is it my
offer right okay for the men in the room
which is like 99% of you women what
what's going on represent here you got
you get close to right but let's just
talk about the men if you have a hot
wife do you hide her in the
closet you show that you show that woman
off
everywhere I was going to say something
else but my my wife would hear it if I
did right you show it off you got to
treat your offer like a hot woman or if
you're a woman treat her like a hot man
right I don't know treat her like Denzel
okay you got to extend the gift and then
you give them an overview this is where
people [__] this up you if you can't
sell your product in one sentence you
can't can't sell it in 10
slides now you will do both but sell it
in one sentence because that will give
that Clarity write your pitch with one
slide on it that sells your entirety of
your product in a single solitary
sentence and then you run the breakdown
breakdown looks like this three to five
to seven components you reveal all major
elements of the core offer this is the
framework you can use headline three
benefits proof in future Pace headline
is what it is three benefits are the
three coolest things that make it
awesome proof because if you say it it
doesn't mean it's true
so if I say Russell has learned from me
I should play a video of him saying I'm
the greatest salesp person in the world
right and then future Pace what life
will be like once they complete it if
you can bring the future into the
present it's is if they've already done
it that's what you should do when you
sell
okay that's the element formula and then
you have access I see people forget this
every day your customers if they can't
visualize how they get your product
they're less likely to buy your product
think of it like a kid underneath a
Christmas tree at Christmas unpacking it
how do they actually get what you sell
how is it actually delivered what are
the logistics behind it people miss this
all the time now this is boring this is
why we put this up front to get it out
of the way but it's necessary it's not
sufficient but it's necessary and this
is how you can introduce a core offer
and if you did it right the audience is
now dying how much is it and where can I
go if I want to buy it and that's we
give them price next nobody can make a
decision to buy something unless they
first know what price it is until they
know the price they can't decide if they
want to buy it or not that's why I put
the price up front so they can decide if
they want to buy it or not and then we
give them more reasons to decide whether
they buy it after we give them the first
one but let's talk
price again many Frameworks I could
teach you if you own all my stuff then
you have most of them but here's the
easiest one I can teach you right now
results compare normal and special so
the results are your own results so if
I'm selling an info product I say hey
info products for me if I'm teaching
people to create info products info
products to me are worth 4 million
that's a price anchor $4
million then I say I normally sell
trainings like this if we were to do
them in person for
$5,000 then I say if you get it from the
website it's about
,000 however if you act fast enough
sprinkle the scarcity in you can get it
one time for $4.99 or three monthly
installments of1 194
anchor 4 million down to
194 that sounds almost free doesn't
it that's how you price anchor four
million is where we started at and then
we ended at 194 and then we add the
scarcity now do people buy here some of
them buy if you do what I just told you
pick up the first wave of buyers
congratulations you just got a C+ on
your
webinar you showed up I'm happy I'm
happy for you you made some money
congratulations but they ain't going to
roll out the red carpet for you you
ain't going to Keynote webinar con
2025 yet okay you get the buyers
everyone else gets now 80% of winning is
showing up so when in doubt pitch
something out that's not bad strategy
but we want to do better do you want to
do better yeah you want to break records
all right good just don't break
mine unless we're partnering together
all right the bone B are what can make
or break you when it comes to getting
the extra sales that otherwise you would
leave money on the table with so every
Market looks like this there's this uh
10810 rule 10% will buy no matter what
they want it you just happen to be there
in front of them they're like it's a
sign from God here's my money 10% of
them will never buy you say I don't want
this Ferrari anymore I'm going to become
a monk take my possessions away from me
they're like I don't trust you and you
can't give a Ferrari away to some people
they just won't take it 80% of the
market could go either way they're
by something they're by seexual they're
by textual I don't know I haven't worked
that one out yet right they will go
either way they will or won't buy given
the right amount of information and
bonuses are one of the easiest ways to
get them to buy so let's talk bonuses
lots of different ways you can use
bonuses oh my God there's so many ways
you could use bonuses I know more about
bonuses than I know about core offers I
know more about bonuses than just about
anything besides objections so I'm going
to give you the quickest game I can give
you in the limited time that we have
here today modalities objection scarcity
andof modalities first simple thing you
can do to massively increase the value
of any webinar offer that you ever make
what is a modality Jason a modality is
the vehicle in which the bonus is
delivered
in so if I sell you a car and then say
here's five more cars how much
additional value is
that no wrong you should F the shap I'm
kidding right thank you for I mean you
got one car how many more cars you need
maybe another one maybe another one I
mean some of you rich [__] you got
like seven cars and you only drive one
of them right so that's a
vehicle but would you rather have six
cars or a car a boat a plane a
motorcycle an ATV a helicopter right
this is different Vehicles each vehicle
gets you from one place to another but
they're different
experiences what sounds better what more
sounds more valuable six cars or six
different unique specific types of
vehicles when you give somebody multiple
things it multiplies the value when you
give them more of the same incremental
at best sometimes it takes away from it
if I have the best clothes in the world
and I give you 360 more closes you say
if that first clothes was so good why do
I need the rest right now you do need
the rest but the perception if they're
not understood you could [__] up a sell
that was closed you could close it so we
want multiple modalities so when I sold
asm5 when we did the $9.8 million this
isn't even all of them this is just some
of them we have group coaching we have a
live event we have software we have
video training we have done for you we
have an app we have a community this
could literally be the same thing but
just delivered in different vehicles and
they say whoa I've never seen value like
this before because they've never seen
an offer like this before they can't
compare it to something else they can
only compare it to how well you sell
so if you do nothing else add multiple
modalities to your offers second create
offer or create bonuses that kill
objections over half the bonuses I
create are meant to shine a spotlight on
one key objection and just destroy it so
every one of you have customers who have
this as an objection how long does it
take before I see a result like yeah
it's like oh let me get on my crystal
ball and predict your future I don't
know how long it takes Jesus Christ
right how long long does it take to make
a baby
right two minutes
right I mean we call that hyper
efficiency right I can turn any
objection into a benefit all right
that's why we create a
bonus if it needs to be done fast
because rents due by the end of the
month and you ain't got the money well
then you're going to want to use bonus
number one and I always caveat it I say
this is not the best approach you will
cut Corners you will hate life but if
you absolutely positively must get it
done as quick as possible if you must
cook the baked potato in 5 minutes in
the microwave we got you and they say oh
I can no longer use that as an excuse
anymore huh maybe I should buy and then
somebody else will say well Jason what
if I try this and I will and I screw it
up what if I mess it up and I say cool I
got eyes on you so when you do mess it
up because you will I will tell you stop
that and then I will unmess it up for
you right and if by some small chance
you actually do something right I will
encourage you applaud you and tell you
to do more of that and that's a bonus
the bonus is when you mess it up here's
how I will stop you okay you ever seen
those packages of peanuts that say
warning may contain peanuts on them
right that's because some idiot
somewhere messed it up and they put the
warning sign on it right hair dryer
don't use in the shower right I will be
that for you that's the bonus all right
what if I can't get get started so most
of your clients this is the thing that
stops them not getting the end result
doing the first step so you offer them a
bonus my favorite bonus is a done for
you just for step one two reasons reason
number one easy to fulfill it costs me
very little I have to do all of it for
them I just have to do the first step
reason number two kills the objection I
can't get started of course you can't
get started I know you can't get started
so I will break into your house I will
grab you by the neck I will shove you in
the shower put water on your face put
the clothes on you put you in front of
the computer and Bang Your Head on the
keyboard until it gets done they say
okay I'll buy thank you right that's the
attitude that's the objection
okay scarcity and bonuses is the most
powerful scarcity you can't buy this
anywhere else at any price it's
exclusive and it's
free is it really
free no
if it was free they could get it but if
they buy a and get B for free it's the
greatest marketing of all time free is
the most powerful word you can use in
your marketing free has made me more
money than anything you can't have it
but you can get it for free and they say
cool they don't look about I gotta buy
this thing anymore the focus isn't on
buying it's on free I want free free
free is this starting to make sense okay
this is is where the money comes from
this makes sense and it makes dollars
all right proof you should prove
everything as much as humanly possible
you should treat your webinar like
you're on trial for a murder you didn't
commit and you have 27 witnesses that
can put you at the place that wasn't
where the murder is at and if I was your
lawyer and I said Hey listen you got 27
Witnesses let's just call two of them
that should be good enough shouldn't it
you'd be like [__] get out of here
right fire my ass right if you got 27
Witnesses you them all now the one area
where people forget this at most is in
the bonuses if they make a claim like oh
this thing is awesome you got to bring
the
receipts you got to bring the receipts
so once when Russell Russell uh he
acquired John Reese's traffic secrets
that and he paid him a million dollars
to acquire that IP and I told him this I
said in your bonus say this bonus is
worth a million dollars cuz that's what
I paid for it and then I said show the
wire transfers because ain't nobody
going to believe you actually paid John
ree's ass a million dollars so show it
and he did so if you guys are running
events that cost a lot of money show the
invoices say this is how important your
success is to me that I'm willing to pay
$562,000 just for the coffee because
that's what it costs at events like this
you know $75 cookies I've paid all of
that in more right bring the receipts
okay you guys want some hacks okay this
is the [__] where you can be lazy not
really pay pay attention and still make
a lot of money which is what I know most
of you
want bonus number one or monetize your
bonuses hack number one not in some
cheesy way we're going to do a coaching
call psyche it's a sales call got you
not like that that's stupid okay not a
discovery call where we discover how
much money you have and how much you'll
give to me right not that kind of call
right you know what the best sales pitch
in the world is it isn't a webinar it's
your
product that's the best sales pitch in
the world and so what we would do
especially uh bonus number three
training with Ben Cummings this was a
$300 a month continuity program we' give
him two months for free that increases
conversion and then we tell them on day
57 we're kicking you out of the program
we're not letting you
continue unless you ask us for a link to
sign up and those first 57 days were so
good so amazing that we made millions of
dollars from this bonus it increased the
front
end and it made a badass back end
everybody sees the ASM results which you
guys don't know that 9.8 we made more
than that on the back
end we made a lot
more crazy just don't tell my ex-wife
okay I'm kidding my yeah
anyway you guys ain't split testing
enough let's just put it that
way so all of these in all of these in
Orange are monetized in the back end
we'll do your first product sourcing for
you for free and then after that you got
to pay us for more and they do because
the first one was amazing uh third party
software you can use a version of this
for free but once you hit a certain
level if you want to upgrade you can
upgrade and we get a cut of that and I
would tell those people when I sell it I
hope all of you upgrade but you'll only
upgrade once you start selling products
in Amazon and by that point I would
rather have you upgrade from inside the
house than have to go out and find
software so I found it for you use it
first when it's useful upgrade later and
we made millions of dollars on the back
of free bonuses this is how you make a
killer offer it's hard to put bonuses in
your offer because it's expensive to you
it costs you time and money so how do
you make the time and money to you so
small that you can put as much of this
in as possible so you could create an
offer nobody can match that's a that's a
million-dollar Insight if ever there was
one and then use third party bonuses you
don't have to create them yourself so I
go to software providers and I say
listen I love your soft software here's
what I need from you two things one I
need to be able to give it away for free
two I need you to change something about
this software so it's Unique to me and
then three give me an exclusivity on it
and I can do that without paying a
single dollar for third party software
you want to know why why do you suppose
that is by the
way yeah I say to them listen how much
you guys pay to acquire a
customer and they say what
first of all I say I don't know most of
the time right whatever right it's just
business who really gives a [__] about
the numbers
right and so you got to have this
attitude it's like detached curiosity
it's the best sales mindset you could
ever be in it's like I'm better to sell
this thing you if you're smart enough
you'll buy it if you're not smart enough
not my problem right it's kind of that
attitude but I go to them but I say
listen it cost you this much these guys
are going to be paying $3,500 to me
would you like a $3,500 buyer for free
and then as long as your software works
they will upgrade for you and I will
encourage them to upgrade does that
sound like a fair deal deal to you and
they say where have you been my whole
life now nine out of 10 of them won't
get that because they're dumb we don't
make our business by dealing with dumb
people but we need to talk to nine dumb
people to find one smart person but
these days you could throw a rock and
hit six guys that have a sass startup
somewhere right so one of those six is
not dumb enough to say no to free money
the other five are so make a deal with
all of them and get one of them to work
for you this is what we would do we put
software into our stuff your customers
are going to find other things they need
anyway so a don't get any money for it
and hope they find a good provider or B
get money and put them with the best
provider I don't know which one you
should pick I'll leave it for you to
decide right make one bonus
blind don't tell what it is just tell
what it does what is it you got to buy
to find out that that Curiosity Factor
alone we'll pick up another point or two
in conversion another point or two in
conversion another point or two in
conversion all right here's how you
should sell if you've done it right when
you introduce the product and then you
said this is how much it is to get
started they're focused on cost they say
product cost a lot and they say oh and
when you sign up you also get this bonus
and you also get this bonus and you also
get this bonus and you also get this
bonus and now's where's the focus at
value start on price end on value most
of you got it twisted you start on value
you end on price you ain't got nowhere
to
go let's change that
okay now we get into risk my favorite
part of the
webinar this is what separates the men
from the
boys the women from the girls the trans
from whatever they are these days I
don't know
right we're not recording any any of
this are we
yeah and what and what you're about to
see next will be deleted from the
webinar con slide and that's when I sell
you okay maybe I'll do that a little bit
maybe I'll do that a little bit all
right
risk you can do an unconditional
guarantee which is for any reason or no
reason at all if it's within the first
30 days if you want your money back you
got it just email us at blah blah blah
blah blah and that's okay yeah we do
that sometimes not my favorite thing to
do but it's better than nothing right I
prefer if nothing else doing a
conditional guarantee Hey listen just do
the bare minimum and then after you do
the bare minimum if you think it's worth
anything less than 100% of what you paid
if you're not 100% thrilled I'll give
you 100% of your money back and you
could do a conditional guarantee I like
those better they net profit more you
don't convert as much point a sale but
who gives a [__] you net profit more so
you will take a small percentage
decrease on conversion but you will
increase the net profit of your clients
with a conditional guarantee I much
prefer a better than money back
guarantee yeah this is this is the best
outside of my own webinars I've every
webinar I've analyzed 0 one% of them use
a better than money back
guarantee I have to look at a thousand
webinars to see one of them do a
legitimate true better than money back
guarantee this is insanity it's crazy
you can keep it simple Vance and I were
talking about this uh on day one when I
came in so this is a $500 product and I
say listen if you buy this product and
you don't double your money in 60 days
I'll give you double your money how's
that for a pitch by the way right pretty
powerful I said here's all you have to
do to qualify once in the morning and
once in the night you got to create a
Google Document share the Google
document with our team so we you can't
cheat it as the time stamps in it and
then in the morning tell me what you're
going to do that day with the product
and in the
evening document what you actually did
that day do that for 60 days straight
and if you do only that and nothing more
and you don't double your money I'll pay
you double your
money now who actually does
that okay let me tell you a story those
who do it don't need the guarantee
because there's nothing more than
consistency consistency more than
anything gets the
result how do you write a
book one word at a time consistency I
don't want to close every sale I just
want to close the next sale that's every
sale by the way did you get that some of
you got that some of you drank too much
last night some of you smoked too much
last night right all right consistency
if they do it they don't need the
guarantee if they don't do it they don't
deserve the
guarantee you get it it's called a
double
bind in in LP terms this is called a
double bind whether you do or you don't
do it I win either way and if you do it
I win more I want you to do it this will
increase the efficacy of your product
you will get more success stories this
way it also increases conversion this is
a simple way now you can get Advanced
with it warning you will try to phone
this in when will and I sit down and we
construct better than money back
guarantees it's a six-hour ordeal it's
typically three two-hour meetings one to
IDE ideate it one to kind of rough in
the first draft and then one to finalize
it it's six hours generally speaking
okay it's high risk High reward but it
looks kind of like this if I had to
summarize it very quickly these eight
steps do not take a picture just pay
attention I saw you put that phone down
right put that phone down I'll give you
the slides right I'm an approachable
nice young man right first thing you do
is object the objection the risk isn't
the money that you put into the program
that's peanuts the risk is all the other
money you're going to
spend you know some of you who get into
yoga you don't just take the yoga class
you're like a walking talking Lulu
liming [__] billboard right that
shit's more expensive than yoga the yoga
is like 15 bucks a class the Lululemon
shirt is like
$6,279 right so when somebody buys your
product they start buying everything
else related to you and 15 other idiots
that are in the program right they buy
everything so the real risk isn't them
losing their money in the course it's
them losing money beyond the course so
you you mention that you actually bring
that up and then you sell the outcome
the outcome is you don't want your money
back anyway because then you're back to
where you started the customer doesn't
want to get their money back they want
to be further along than where they were
started so give them that further along
Target specifically this is what I will
have you doing by this
date and I will remove the additional
risk you have to take to go after the
Target that I
present and then I will I will in case
of emergency break glass and give you an
extra special resource I've held back
only for people that are attempting to
qualify for this better than money back
guarantee and then if it still doesn't
work I will throw you aside I will step
in your place and I will try to get the
result for you and then if I can't do
that I'll just give you a pile of
money you ever sell like that no that's
why you never got results like this yet
this is how you sell for the big bucks
this is big boy stuff this is big girl
stuff you ready for Big Boy big girl
stuff okay you ain't ready yet not yet
not yet you you maybe two of you are
okay I will teach you
more you gotta prove it remember this
you got to prove it so I said just in
case I have to buy all y'all businesses
I got a million dollars in a bank
account C asde just to do that because
if you can't make it work I'll make it
work and they go okay all right want to
all right somebody serious today and if
he's serious selling I'm serious buying
if you ain't serious selling they ain't
serious
buying facts right there facts and then
you you put the conditions you could be
very thorough with the conditions I
expect a lot from you I'm giving you a
lot so therefore I expect a lot from you
here's what you need to do so we
typically make these consumption bonus
or uh cons consumption conditions just
do these 34
things I mean you laugh but do you think
like think about a webinar how hard is
it to do a webinar it's [__] hard I
know more than anybody it's very hard
why did we do them because it's because
it's hard it's valuable the few of us
who can do it make the most amount of
money I sell I don't know if You' guys
saw the goat webinars pitch that I do
the the newest one but it's like you saw
that right tell me if I don't start off
this way I say I'm gonna start off this
webinar in a weird sort of way by
admitting all the flaws challenges and
problems when it comes to webinars I'm
going to tell you all the ways in which
webinars are hard and which they're
tough and in all the different
deficiencies related to a webinar I flat
out start the webinar that way admitting
all the flaws problems and challenges
and then I say but before you know it I
will have wrapped a net around you a
buyer's net and by the end of this
presentation you'll have no other choice
to buy than what I'm selling you today
you'll have no other choice to buy it if
you're the kind of person who blah blah
blah you get the rest of it right so I
say up front here's all the problems all
the challenges all the issues and this
is true with anything you sell there's a
lot of moving Parts don't pretend there
isn't but hey if they're enrolled in a
better tomorrow they will do those
moving parts so don't shy away from them
make them your conditions and then hit
the objections hit them like a pro okay
I'm going to give you the elementary
version of doing objections which will
probably be blow mind-blowing for you
okay but it's like oh child you don't
know you don't know yet you don't know
what I can show you right I'm I'm like
you don't know till you know it's like
I'm Morpheus in The Matrix I'm like man
by the time we're done I'm going to show
you how to dodge bullets right now by
the time we're done done you don't even
need to dodge
bullets does that make sense okay some
of y'all still dodging bullets when I'm
closing I look at the bullets and say
ha falls to the ground that's how you
sell you want to sell like that
[__] validate reframe close again I
could teach you many many many many
models I could teach you a model that's
the opposite of this and it still works
the opposite of a thing is often as good
as the thing so can I can teach a model
where I disagree with them but that's
advanced stuff we'll talk basic stuff
right validate reframe close somebody
says it cost too much here's a really
easy one for you validate it it's smart
you're looking to get the most for your
money
right you turn it into a positive and
then you reframe it in order for this to
be the best purchase you ever made what
would have to be true and they go oh
because if you give somebody a Target
they look at the Target if you give
something to focus on they focus on do
you see my point
you focus on it right and then you close
would it need to have this or perhaps
also this and what about this what if it
had all of these things plus it had this
and plus it had this and plus it had
this then would it be good enough for
you to get started today at example.com
yes which you will go to now and you get
the rest right validate reframe close
here's another one what if I fail yeah
left to your own devices you'll totally
fail you validate it right then you
reframe it what if there was
a way to ensure that you couldn't
sabotage your own success though H and
they say what's that and then you close
you say failure pisses me off so much
that I won't let you fa on my watch
which is why I put this in here which is
why I put this in here and which is why
I put this in there and my freaking
product is on hands and knees begging
you right now please buy me please buy
me and if you're any kind of a person
who's respectable at all you will go to
url.com right now and sign up and
they're like okay
and they sign up not everybody but
that's a tool and toolkit and then I
take the next toolkit next tool and
toolkit out and I try that one right
this is basic stuff right validate
reframe close I don't have the next I
don't have another example but they say
to do it in sets of Threes what's one
more
objection see you're all in a trance
right now this is hypnosis right Eli
taught you about it now I'm doing it on
you right yeah yeah sh don't tell
anybody right I gotta go talk to my wife
you got to go talk to your wife okay and
when you talk to her what is the first
three things you're going to say to her
about how great this presentation is
today it's Jason [__] flin right and
if Jason were to offer you Consulting to
help you grow your business even further
and it was the stupidest deal of the
century and it made sense to you then
would you say yes to it today he already
did right validate reframe close you
could do the opposite it costs too much
of course it costs too much that's why
you're going to buy it because you don't
buy cheap [__] you buy the best don't
you yes I do go here and sign up right
now it's a tool got many of them okay
you can also just read scripts this is
Ben coming he did a million dollars in
three days on his first webinar
following and he says listen I'm just
going to read what my mentor taught me
and then he read all 53 of
these why not right Zoom doesn't charge
you by the
minute PowerPoint doesn't charge you by
the slide right the reason most of you
don't close much is because you you're
either aill literate or you don't have
the book so I don't think you're
illiterate so you just don't have the
book right I will give you one you want
one of these closes okay you want it
okay okay I'm not I'm the cow I don't
give all the milk for free I just give a
little drop or two you got to buy the
cow to get all the milk right this one's
hardcore some of you don't have the the
guts to do this yet I feel sorry for you
I'd like to help you change that right
but nonetheless here it is when you sign
up not only going to get the best deal
you're going to get something more you
ever heard of the poem called Footprints
poem goes like this man had a dream he
was walking on the beach with God God
and as he walked many moments from his
life were shown in the sky and during
certain moments he only saw one set of
footprints and at other moments he saw
two sets of footprints and the man
noticed something he said wow during the
hardest points of my life there was only
one set of footprints and this got the
man upset and he got pissed and in his
pissed state of mind he said to God he
said God during the hardest darkest
moments of my life you left me to walk
alone and God said Son those times when
you only see one set of footprints
that's when I carried you
and when you sign up at example.com
yes not only are you getting the best
bill ever you're also getting the best
support ever and with me if things ever
get hard and you need carried I will
carry that
ass I will support you I will be there
for you so help me help you by signing
up that example that yes
you know what branding is right it's
just repeated exposure to a concept
until it becomes ingrained in your brain
i Brand the URL you guys ain't branding
the URL enough
right the biggest problem with
objections though is this you're only
using them in the clothes I'm using them
everywhere when we did this this was the
script now I've templatized it I am
confident you could use this script in
almost any offer and I will prove to you
after I show you the script but pay very
close attention and I I will give you
the slides I will give you the slides so
be present all right
presentation that's what you should do
when you present you should be present
all right you guys ready ready okay let
me set your expectation for today's
webinar I believe it'll be the single
greatest thing you've ever seen when it
comes to insert topic here how's that
for hype by the way see when it comes to
this I know you better than you know
yourself I know your problems more than
you know them over the last year and my
hope is if I know your struggles better
than you I can give you better solutions
to them than you can find anywhere else
and here are the things that you think
get in the way you think that your money
is limited you think that you don't have
the time you think you lack confidence
and skills and abilities and stupid
stuff like that you're scared to get out
of your comfort zone plus if I had to
guess you're overwhelmed by bright shiny
objects and you let little things get in
the way of making big decisions and you
don't have enough support from the loved
ones and from the other people in your
life and most marketers who pretend to
have a solution for your problem
actually don't have a solution for you
you face confusion and you face conflict
on a daily basis and with that in mind
I'm nervous your discount what I'm about
to share with you today you'll think it
ain't worth replacing what I'm already
trying to do to solve my problem Jason
and you may think huh I don't even
believe what you can do will work for me
or you might think oh is this just
another big setup for another big fancy
sales
pitch you may even think what I share is
cool but eh it's not that good and you
may even think you've tried already what
I'm about to show you even though
there's no possible way in heaven or
Earth that you could have ever tried to
do it the way I'll exactly show it but
if I don't address these issues up front
then it ain't GNA matter what I do
afterwards because if I don't share
anything with you that first doesn't
address these objections you will
immediately reject it you will
immediately kick it out our time today
will be wasted if I can't get you to put
your biases and excuses on hold for the
next 57 minutes who cares then if I show
you this great result or this great
result or this great result or this
great result or this this this and this
great result if I show them to you you
may think oh well you got lucky or you
may think I faked those that they're not
even real that I somehow made them up
where you may think it was a miracle or
one in a million chance that no mere
human could replicate however hopefully
you're also possibly thinking maybe it
is right with the right approach maybe I
if I follow just some of that maybe I
can get some of those results maybe it's
worth me being at least open-minded for
the next 57 minutes and that's all I ask
is that you just be open-minded let me
show you the exact specific approach
I've perfected to get the results you're
so desperate and hopeful for I'll lay it
out for you step by step and then you
can draw your own conclusions does that
sound
[Applause]
fair that's the first cell not buy my
product does that sound fair okay sales
are a series of that lead to the big yes
okay run the numbers less than three
minutes 42 slides 17 objections and oh
by the way because I'm showing off now I
snuck an eight proof elements did you
catch that most of you don't have eight
proof elements in your whole
presentation I snuck them in in the
first three minutes right crazy [__]
crazy [__] uh have chat GPT do that for
you good luck right you don't need AI
you need
ji I got jokes I got jokes okay just
don't tell Tony and and Dean this right
because Tony and Dean just paid me
$62,000 just for a webinar outline
that's my rate just for an outline right
just for the tip
right same script same script listen
listen when you paint the Mona Lisa once
you don't repaint it you just hand that
[__] out all right I'm handing out Mona
Lisa some of you are art collectors some
of you don't know where you're at right
now hopefully you figure it out
right once you figure it out though it's
easy you install it done right
objections are powerful in the intro
they're just as powerful in the
transition the transition is the bridge
between the content and the offer if you
saw this this was the biggest book
launch of all time when Alex sold his
hundred million doll leads he did a
webinar he paid me to help him with that
webinar he used my two choices cloth
before the presentation today I was
faced with one of two choices the first
one is to leave you on your own in a
cold dark miserable existence the second
option is to do everything I can to help
you succeed lucky for you I chose the
second option and when I did you'll be
absolutely thrilled what I have for you
today and that's an objection the
transition goes from oh you're going to
pitch me something to thank you for
making me an offer thank you for making
me an offer that's how you should set up
your
offer and what about
you should I leave you on your
own in a dark
miserable
cold
lonely terrible Str struggle to figure
out how to implement what I shared with
you today should I be that cruel and
mean and heartless to you to let you try
to figure it out on your
own or should I make you an offer so
stupid that you'll question my sanity
should I make you an
offer yeah okay now I didn't know I
could make an offer until last Monday
it's like seven days ago or something
like that they go like you want to make
you want to make an offer Jason I'm like
that's like asking a crack addict if
they want some
crack so I rewrote my whole presentation
because everything I did was a setup to
make you an offer oops right now what
I'm doing is dangerous here I'm pitching
a room full of pitch people kids don't
try this at
home this is walking the tight RPP
without a net okay I am teaching brain
surgery to brain surgeons while
operating on their
brains this could blow up it'll be fun
to see what happens right most of you
are sellers but you're not buyers you
see yourself as presenters but not
attendees you don't go to webinars you
do webinars I'm told this is the hardest
audience to sell [__] it let's see if I
can do it right here's the thing though
you guys are all really good I mean I
tease you and I kind of get you going
and all that but you're the best of the
best you guys are kicking serious ass
here's what I've learned about clients
who kick serious ass they get complacent
they're okay with eight out of 10 they
don't know how much money 10 out of 10
is the difference you know what eight
out of 10 is it's 1.7 on a leaderboard
you know what 10 out of 10 is it's 9.8
on a
leaderboard the difference between
amazing and one of a kind is inches it's
not miles good is the enemy of great so
most of you are really good and I can
make you great but you're the most
resistant to great because you're
already pretty good you're not like my
young clients who are like I got to show
Daddy that I can make it on my own he'll
[__] do anything I tell him you guys
are like I made a million that's good
enough right so let's see if I can help
you okay of those that I can help the
most in the world there's not a better
room of people that I can help than you
in this room right now that's a fact
that's why I'm doing this right so I'm
gonna make you a once ever offer that
only a narcissist wouldn't
buy this is how you close how you close
okay this is how you close okay
I gave you just the tip today did daddy
do good Daddy did good did he yeah just
a little bit though I didn't give you
the full total webinar knowledge that I
could have possibly give because it's
impossible to do it in 60 minutes I
couldn't do it in three
days okay I could give you go webinar
some of you own it I know you told me
you owned it good for you smart that's
it retails for about 2,500 bucks at go
webinars.com that has way more knowledge
than what I talked about today okay this
is a better course than the one Alex
bought that he said was the single best
course that he ever bought on offer in
Persuasion this is even better than that
okay I can give you my 32 best webinar
slide decks Joe Mcall right these are
the 32 best pitches of all time the
Michelson twins uh took one of these
slide decks and buil a hundred million
doll webinar out of it and it's 80% the
same stuff I don't care if you steal
from me as long as you pay me and give
me credit okay once you're am my a
client you can use my [__] if you're not
a client of mine I don't like it you're
stealing it yeah here's my 53 closes you
can take them and make them your own and
you should or you can just read them
okay get it going and then get it right
I also could give you murder the
objection I did this in person it was
5,000 John Anderson who's part of a
knowledge Source he actually attended
this and paid this Mark Anthony Bates is
another one who paid it I put Mark's
invoice up here because he paid me twice
the first half of the first day was so
good he came up to me and he says can I
give you another
$5,000 and I said hm let me think about
that for a tenth of a second yes of
course you can right that's how good
this training is so we talked about
objections today this is two days of me
going into objection smashing these are
the best of the best techniques okay um
I have go offers I'm going to launch it
next year and I typically charge 10,000
when I initially launch these courses
this is going to give every little in
insight and advice and if you hear a
ringing then it tells you that this is
absolutely a sign from God that you
should buy this
product it's true yeah opport
opportunity Rings these days it doesn't
knock and I'm going to show you how to
do that in your offers okay this has
never been released
before when I do trainings like this
500% increase in sale about 100%
Improvement 102 sales on a webinar from
220 attendees 67 book calls highest show
rate highest close rate some of you were
in these trainings okay this is a
typical customer result that went
through my coaching when I did a webinar
coaching program 420 calls book 540k in
4 days I could give you that I could
also give you my automation software I
guess the cool kids these days are
calling it as if live I've never heard
that ter before I think it's pretty
slick right this is as if software this
allows you to do automated webinars and
I could give you Consulting with me
which is arguably the greatest thing
because technique don't mean [__] if you
don't know the context in which to apply
it in so my eyes on your stuff best eyes
you could ever possibly have I charge
$7,000 for two hours of Consulting some
of you have paid me for that already
awkward you see what I'm about to do
next right
yeah unlike some who price
anchor they say I'm worth this much but
nobody pays them I am booked full at my
rate of 3,500 bucks an
hour aka the rate of eight brain
surgeons that's what it would take to
charge that much and some of you here
have already paid me for that now this
would be a stupid offer for me to put
all this together and offer it up to you
because not only am I going to do it at
a huge discount from what it actually
retails for for I got to split the money
whatever I sell at an event like this
half of it goes to the organizers so I'm
really working for minimum wage here
this is not good for me it's good for
you at the expense of me all right there
are easier ways for me to make money so
then why would I do it this way why do
you think I would make this
offer you're my people I care about
you I care about you you're my people I
know I can help you if you're drowning
and I could easily reach down and pull
you out it's my moral obligation to do
that if I can help you get to the next
level I will help you get to the next
level I will do
that so here's the offer write it down I
don't got much time to go through it I
have a hard limit on this quick
expiration two hours of Consulting with
me you can do whatever you want with it
it can be webinars it can be anything
you want just fill out of form before
each call so I can best serve you you
get the recording you just must redeem
this in 90 days my calendar is literally
book full so I need to know if you're in
or out you get these book it in the next
90 days okay you get my go webinars uh
coaching program single best webinar
training I've ever done we've released
it we haven't even really marketed it
yet you some of what it includes is my
32 best slide decks and all my best
webinar closes again you can just read
these word for word okay you get the
recordings to the goat coaching program
which was $10,000 uh I know Manny you
were in the program was that like the
best program you ever been a part of the
greatest coaching program he's ever been
a part of and Manny is a buyer all right
so you should listen to him yeah
just some of the results this is average
results you get the recordings of that
okay you get one year of our software
we're going to retail the bottom level
of that for $99 a month top level for
$299 a month you get a whole year of
that isn't released yet when it's
released you'll get first dibs on that
okay you get the murder the objection
training and then you get the goat
offers we haven't launched this yet when
we do off launch this you will get the
recordings of this this is going to be
eight weeks 2our sessions each 16 hours
of me going through the very best of the
best of offers because if Alex can teach
it to you after he learned it from me I
think I can teach it to you better so
you get this as well this is an
exclusive offer I will never make it
again this is legitimately two-hour
Consulting
$7,000 actual retail value not [__]
marketer value not fictitious it could
be worth this much it actually is worth
this much the go webinars program sells
for this much
$2,497 the recordings from our coaching
when we did it is $10,000 program when
the auto software is at least
$1,188 murder the objection does go for
$1,500 at murderthe objection. comom go
offers isn't released yet what it is
we'll do a $10,000 coaching program sell
the recordings for
$2,497 I'm not good at math so I had to
add this up ahead of time
24,000 that's not a [__] number you
get that right that's an actual retail
value number webinar con only special
pricing less than
$3,000 that's half of one hour less than
one hour of just my Consulting alone you
get it all this is the QR code if you
don't know how to scan a QR code this is
the URL go webinars.com weinar con we're
going to lunch next after lunch I am
telling my team take the offer down
because as much as I love you guys if 40
of you buy this that's 80 hours of my
time that's [__] insane right if 60
of you buy this I am going to question
my choices in life right I don't know if
this makes sense for you to buy it or
not I don't know who will buy it I know
some of you were already ready to buy
told you no because I wanted everybody
to buy at once because it's a nice
dopamine rush for me right and it's good
bragging later sometimes you got to do
[__] just to say you can do it so this
is me making you the mafia offer the
best of all offers that I possibly can
it is 100% limited though because my
time is limited just as your time is
limited so if you truly are committed to
webinars I would love to commit myself
to help you get to the next level with
webinars my name is Jason flon has been
an honor and a privilege to serve each
and every one of you today I appreciate
you and I'll be here for the rest of the
whole time